Finding Aid for Carol T. Mowbray papers, 1973-2006
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Projects, 1986-2005
  - Washtenaw-Genesee Homeless Project
    - Interim Report, 1990 (Box 10)
    - Technical Reports, 1992 (Box 10)
  - Washtenaw Housing Alliance, 1998 (Box 10)
- Publications, 1973-2006
  The Publications series (2.2 linear feet) is organized by year published. The first folder, "Bibliography" contains a thorough listing of Carol Mowbray's publications and serves as an index for the many publications Carol has written. Researchers should consult the "Bibliography" to find specific articles and publications. The publications series is not comprehensive, but does contain the articles found within her papers. Located after the articles are materials corresponding to her book projects and other materials.
  - Bibliography, 1997-2005 (Box 10)
  - 1973-1990, 17 folders (Box 10)
  - 1991-2002, 20 folders (Box 11)
  - 2003-2006 (Box 12)
  - Undated, 2 folders (Box 12)
  - APPI Textbook, 2000 (Box 12)
  - Consumers as Providers, 1997 (Box 12)
  - Editor Thank-You Letters, 2000-2001 (Box 12)
  - Supported Education Book, 1995-2000; 2 folders (Box 12)